http://importshark.com/catalog/privacy.php/osCsid/355d26ae769917a876d8454d092999ff

Cart ContentsCheckoutMy Account
Top » Catalog » Importshark Privacy Notice
Importshark Privacy Notice
Your Privacy
At Importshark we are committed to maintaining the trust and confidence of our customers as well as visitors to our web site. In particular, we want you to know that Importshark is not in the business of selling, renting or trading your information with other companies and businesses for marketing purposes.
Collection and Use of Personal Information
Personal information means any information that may be used to identify you, such as, your name, title, phone number, email address, or mailing address.
In general, you can browse our web site without giving us any personal information. We use several products to analyze traffic to this web site in order to understand our customers and visitors needs and to continually improve our site for them. We collect only anonymous, aggregate statistics. For example, we do not tie a specific visitor to a specific IP address.
Additional activities on our site require you to be registered—for example, purchasing products, inquiring about a product, submitting product reviews. As part of the registration process, we collect additional personal information. We use that information for several general purposes: to fulfill
an
order made; to contact you if we need to obtain or provide additional information; to contact you regarding an inquiry or product review.
Importshark may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in connection with a sale, merger, transfer, exchange or other disposition (whether of assets, stock or otherwise) of all or a portion of a business of
Importshark and/or its subsidiaries or to (1) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process served on Importshark or this web site; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of Importshark and this web site; (3) enforce its agreements with you, or (4) act in urgent circumstances to protect personal safety or the public.
Credit/Debit Card Information
Importshark uses third party credit/debit card processing services (PayPal). For your protection, and to avoid liability, Importshark is not able to view and or access your card information.
Disclosure of Personal Information
In some instances we rely on our outside vendors to fulfill product purchases—for example, drop shipping from a manufacturer, shipping vendors (USPS, FedEx, UPS ….. etc).
To do this, we may pass your information to them for that purpose only, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.
Children and Privacy
Our web site does not offer information intended to attract children. Importshark does not knowingly solicit personal information from children under the legal driving age.
Use of Cookies
A cookie is a small text file containing information that a web site transfers to your computers hard disk for record-keeping purposes and allows us to analyze our site traffic patterns. A cookie can not give us access to your computer or to information beyond what you provide to us. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies; consult your browsers manual or online help if you want information on restricting or disabling the browsers handling of cookies. If you disable cookies, you can still view the publicly available information on our web site. If are using a shared computer and you have cookies turned on, be sure to log off when you finish.
Links to Other Web Sites
Our web site contains links to information on other web sites. On web sites we do not control, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you provide while visiting those sites. Those sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy, and if you have questions about how a site uses your information, consult that sites privacy statement.
Accessing/Updating Your Personal Information and Unsubscribing
You are entitled to access the personal information that we hold. To access your personal information click on “My Account” and log in using your previously registered information.
From there you may view/update your information or unsubscribe to general mailings at anytime
Your Consent
By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of the information you provide to us as outlined in this Privacy Policy. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and without notice. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will publish those changes on this page.
Continue
Categories Kia Stinger-> (196)Genesis Coupe-> (1206)Genesis G70/G80 (16)Gensis Sedan-> (78)Veloster-> (325)Tiburon-> (302)Sonata-> (100)Elantra-> (110)Kona (3)Tucson (5)Santa Fe (11)Kia Forte-> (58)Kia Optima-> (76)Other Kia's-> (67)Other Hyundai's-> (43)Universal-> (21)
Manufacturers A'PEXiAascoACT ClutchAEMaFe PowerAgency PowerArk PerformanceArtXBoostecBorlaBremboBrenthonBuddy ClubBully ClutchClutchMastersCompetition Clu..CSF RadiatorsCX RacingDBADC SportsEBC BrakesEibachEPRExedyExosExtreme Dimensi..F1 RacingFidanzaGReddyGreenTechGT-SpecH&RHAWKHPSImportsharkIngallsInjenIxion DesignJun BLK SportK&NKW SuspensionLuxonM&S CarartMagnaFlowMedignMobisMyRidesNext Generation..PowerSlotProgress Techno..RalcoRZRally ArmorRoadRunsSarona DesignSeibonSequence-XSPECSpec-DSpyder AutoStopTechSuspension Tech..TanabeTeinTomato A&PVega StyleVISVividVogtlandWeapon-R
Quick Find
Use keywords to find the product you are looking for.Advanced Search
What's New? Ludi Type-A Deck Spoiler$625.00
Information
Shipping & Returns Privacy Notice Conditions of Use Contact Us
Shopping Cart 0 items
Specials Weapon-R Neo Ti Short Ram Intake (2.0L)$255.00$289.00
Reviews Product looks great but install is difficult ..
Bestsellers 3D Steering Wheel BadgeEVGR Stinger v2 Steering Wheel BadgeWing Emblem Center Badge.Black Wing Emblem.Chrome Wing Emblem
Copyright © 2020 importshark.comPowered by osCommerce
